<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><Search><pages Count="6"><page Index="1"><![CDATA[Your Business, Re-imagined.]]></page><page Index="2"><![CDATA[e
                                                                                                  k
                                                                                  F
                                                                                       edbac
     Why
     W  h  y                                                                      Feedback
     Us
          e
     Use
                                                                                       r
                                                                                     eg
                                                                                    t
                                                                                  Integration & Your Feedback Passport
                                                                                        ati
                                                                                                      eedback
                                                                                                    F
                                                                                                              P

                                                                                                Y
                                                                                            n &
                                                                                                  ur
                                                                                                 o
                     ?
               o
                  il
     Ideacoil?                                                                    In e-imagine  y o our business via the  F eedback  assp o r t ® ®  r ategic mar k eting
     Ideac
                                                                                                                assport API. Use the API as st
                                                                                  Re-imagine your business via the Feedback Passport API. Use the API as strategic marketing
                                                                                                               P
                                                                                  R
                                                                                                                                 r
                                                                                                          y
                                                                                                              r
                                                                                                               oject online, or in-pe
                                                                                                                                  ectly to
                                                                                      r
                                                                                       anding channels to distribute
                                                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                                                        our custome
                                                                                                           our p
                                                                                                                             r
                                                                                                                             son di
                                                                                                                                       y
                                                                                  and branding channels to distribute your project online, or in-person directly to your customers
                                                                                  and b
                                                                                                                                                 s
                                 r
                         • Dri
                             e mo
                             v
                                    enue
                                   e
                                    v
                                  r
                         • Drive more revenue
                                 e
                                                                                     our business location.
                                                                                    y
                                                                                   at
                         • Capture customer trends
                         • Captu r e customer t r ends                             at your business location.
                         •  R eal-time analytics tailo r ed to  y our business
                         • Real-time analytics tailored to your business
                                                                                  Insigh t   R e w a r d s ® ®
                                                                                  Insight Rewards
                                                     e
                      e
    W
                      xperience-based
             o
                                           r
        vide kn
              wledge and
                                  eedback on di
       r
                                            ect consumer
     e p
                                                      xperiences. This enables
                                  f
       o
    We provide knowledge and experience-based feedback on direct consumer experiences. This enables   Y Your business provides the reward or a free gift to facilitate the process of collecting feedback,  ,
                                                                                                        r
                                                                                                                                           eedbac
                                                                                                        d or a f
                                                                                                       a
                                                                                             o
                                                                                             r
                                                                                   our business p
                                                                                              vides the
                                                                                                     ew
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                                                                k
                                                                                                             r
                                                                                                                              ocess of collecting
                                                                                                                    acilitate the p
                                                                                                                    f
                                                                                                             ee gift to
                                                                                                                             r
                                                                                                                                           f
               r
                    ofit ma
                                  ease b
                                 r
                 e p
                   r
                 v
                o
                                           alt
                                      r
                                             y
                                      and l
    companies to improve profit margins and increase brand loyalty. .             and encourage Feedbackers to contribute to your brand’s authenticity. Additionally, Ideacoil
                                          o
                                           y
                         gins and inc
    companies to imp
                         r
                                                                                                                    and
                                                                                                                                .
                                                                                                                               y
                                                                                                                       s authenticit
                                                                                                                       ’
                                                                                                                                 A
                                                                                                   e
                                                                                                                y
                                                                                                  k
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                                                         , Ideacoil
                                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                    s to contribute to
                                                                                             F
                                                                                          age
                                                                                         r
                                                                                                                                  dditionall
                                                                                                                 our b
                                                                                                                    r
                                                                                             eedbac
                                                                                  and encou
                                                                                   offers monetary incentives to help boost Feedbacker engagement and transparency with your
                                                                                   of f e r s moneta r y incenti v es to help boost  F eedbac k er engagement and t r anspa r ency with  y our
                                                                                   company. .
                                                                                        y
                                                                                   compan
                                                                                  Li v e  &  In t e r a c t i v e
                                                                                  Live & Interactive
                                                                                  Live Reaction connects you to real-time Feedback, allowing you to reshape your marketing
                                                                                  Li v e  R eaction connects  y ou to  r eal-time  F eedbac k , all o wing  y ou to  r eshape  y our mar k eting
                                                                                  strategy and achieve results.
                                                                                  st r ate g y and achi ev e  r esults.
                                                                                                                            Gain Valuable Insights
                                                                                                                            G a i n   V a l uable  I ns i gh t s
                                                                                                    e
                                                                                                       v
                                                                                                         di
                                                                                                                  r
                                                                                                                                   ghly
                                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                                                         ie
                                                                                                                                          n
                                                                                                    r
                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                                                              n
                                                                                                                                               y
                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                                             i
                                                                                                                                            ed
                                                                                                      i
                                                                                                       e
                                                                                                                                           c
                                                                                                                                               o
                                                                                                                  om
                                                                                                                                  i
                                                                                                                             w
                                                                                                     c
                                                                                                             si
                                                                                                                t
                                                                                                                                      xp
                                                                                                                     ee
                                                                                                                         c
                                                                                                                       dba
                                                                                                                              ho a
                                                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                          k
                                                                                                                                                ur
                                                                                                                                 e
                                                                                                              gh
                                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                  ou

                                                                                                                s
                                                                                                                            s
                                                                                                                 f
                                                                                                           c
                                                                                                 Y You receive direct insights from Feedbackers who are highly experienced in your
                                                                                                                                  h
                                                                                                             in
                                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                           t
                                                                                                                     F
                                                                                                                                        e
                                                                                                           y
                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                         st
                                                                                                   c
                                                                                                    i
                                                                                                    f
                                                                                                 s specific industry. .
                                                                                                  p
                                                                                                   e
                                                                                                     i
                                                                                                       ndu
                                                                                                      i
                                                                                                     c
                                                          U
                                                            NTS IS TH
            Y
                                      , SO WH
        O
                    '
                                N
                                  O
             , THERE
                                                                     E
       T TODAY, THERE'S SO MUCH NOISE, SO WHAT REALLY COUNTS IS THE
                                    S
                                     E
          D
                                   I
                                                   A
           A
                                                    L
                            U
                                               T
                                             A
                                                RE
                     S SO M
                                                      Y
                             CH
                                                         O
                                                        C
                                                     L
                            C
                              T
                             A
             T
                               I
              Y OF
                        UNI
                    OMM
                  C
       QUALITY OF COMMUNICATION, AND IDEACOIL HELPS ME TO ACHIEVE

                                                            T
                                                          E
                                                  H
                                                   ELP
                                                      S M
                                                             O
                                                                   E
                                                                    V
                                                                     E
                                                                  I
       QUA
                                                               A
                                                                CH
                                               IL
                                      D
                                        I
                                         D
                                 N
                                  , A
                                     N
                                             C
                                O
                                              O
                                           A
           LI
                                          E
                                                                                                                           Reliable, Fast & Private
             THAT. THEY KNOW HOW TO ASK THE RIGHT QUESTIONS.
             TH A T .  TH E Y  KN O W H O W  T O  A S K  TH E   RI GHT Q UE S T I O N S .                                  R e l iab l e,   F a s t   &  P r i v a t e
                                                                                                                               e
                                                                                                                                          t
                                                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                                                        e
                                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                                                           u
                                                                                                                                               o
                                                                                                                                                ng
                                                                                                                                            s
                                                                                                                                            t am
                                                                                                                                   hel
                                                                                                                                    p
                                                                                                                                 t
                                                                                                                                 o

                                                                                                                                       s
                                                                                                                                       t
                                                                                                                                     f
                                                                                                                                      o
                                                                                                      o
                                                                                                        c
                                                                                                           e
                                                                                                                    e
                                                                                                       l
                                                                                                          at
                                                                                                                     ngaging d
                                                                                                       i
                                                                                                     c
                                                                                                                            alogu
                                                                                                  Ideacoil creates an upbeat, engaging dialogue to help foster trust among
                                                                                                         e
                                                                                                            s an upbeat,
                                                                                                                           i
                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                  Idea
                                                                                                                                         u
                                                                                                                                          r
                                                                                                            r
                                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                            s and
                                                                                                           e
                                                                                                         c
                                                                                                          k
                                                                                                                                        o
                                                                                                     F
                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                                              ome
                                                                                                                                                 s
                                                                                                                                                r
                                                                                                     Feedbackers and your company. Through our system, your customers
                                                                                                                                           us
                                                                                                                                           c

                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                                             t
                                                                                                       dba
                                                                                                                                   y
                                                                                                                  u
                                                                                                                 o
                                                                                                                                   stem,
                                                                                                                    o
                                                                                                                         . Th
                                                                                                                                  s
                                                                                                                    c
                                                                                                                  r
                                                                                                                     m
                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                                       an
                                                                                                                            ough our
                                                                                                                      p
                                                                                                                           r
                                                                                                                y
         OUTREACH MUSIC FESTIVAL & ACADEMY, SCHWAZ, AUSTRIA
         OUTR E A CH M U S I C FE S T I V A L  &  A C ADEM Y , SCH W AZ, AU S TR I A                   p provide faster, higher quality reviews that only you have access to. .
                                                                                                                                            cc
                                                                                                                        y
                                                                                                                                             e

                                                                                                                             w
                                                                                                                           v
                                                                                                                           i
                                                                                                                            e
                                                                                                                                                o
                                                                                                                                              s
                                                                                                                         r
                                                                                                                              s that
                                                                                                                          e
                                                                                                                                               s t
                                                                                                                        t
                                                                                                               , higher qual
                                                                                                                                      o
                                                                                                            f
                                                                                                                                        a
                                                                                                                                     y
                                                                                                              t
                                                                                                              e
                                                                                                                                      u h
                                                                                                               r
                                                                                                            as
                                                                                                         v
                                                                                                                                  o
                                                                                                        o
                                                                                                                       i
                                                                                                       r
                                                                                                                                   nly
                                                                                                          de
                                                                                                         i
                                                                                                                                          e a
                                                                                                                                         v]]></page><page Index="3"><![CDATA[e
                       k
       F
           edbac
 Why
 W h y  Feedback
 Us
 e
 Use
            r
          eg
         t
       Integration & Your Feedback Passport
             ati
                          eedback
                         F
                                  P

                    Y
                 n &
                      ur
                     o
 ?
 o
 il
 Ideacoil?  In e-imagine  y o our business via the  F eedback  assp o r t ® ®  r ategic mar k eting
 Ideac
                                     assport API. Use the API as st
       Re-imagine your business via the Feedback Passport API. Use the API as strategic marketing
                                    P
       R
                                                      r
                               y
                                   r
                                   oject online, or in-pe
                                                      ectly to
           r
           anding channels to distribute
                                                                    r
                                                            our custome
                                our p
                                                 r
                                                  son di
                                                            y
       and branding channels to distribute your project online, or in-person directly to your customers
       and b
                                                                     s
 r
 • Dri
 e mo
 v
 enue
 e
 v
 r
 • Drive more revenue
 e
         our business location.
         y
       at
 • Capture customer trends
 • Captu r e customer t r ends  at your business location.
 •  R eal-time analytics tailo r ed to  y our business
 • Real-time analytics tailored to your business
       Insigh t   R e w a r d s ® ®
       Insight Rewards
 e
 e
 W
 xperience-based
 o
 r
 vide kn
 wledge and
 eedback on di
 r
 ect consumer
 e p
 xperiences. This enables
 f
 o
 We provide knowledge and experience-based feedback on direct consumer experiences. This enables   Y Your business provides the reward or a free gift to facilitate the process of collecting feedback,  ,
                            r
                                                                eedbac
                            d or a f
                           a
                  o
                 r
        our business p
                  vides the
                         ew
                         r
                                                                    k
                                 r
                                                  ocess of collecting
                                         acilitate the p
                                        f
                                  ee gift to
                                                  r
                                                               f
 r
 ofit ma
 ease b
 r
 e p
 r
 v
 o
 alt
 r
 y
 and l
 companies to improve profit margins and increase brand loyalty. .  and encourage Feedbackers to contribute to your brand’s authenticity. Additionally, Ideacoil
 o
 y
 gins and inc
 companies to imp
 r
                                         and
                                                    .
                                                    y
                                            s authenticit
                                           ’
                                                     A
                       e
                                    y
                      k
                        r
                                                             , Ideacoil
                                                            y
                        s to contribute to
                 F
              age
              r
                                                      dditionall
                                     our b
                                        r
                  eedbac
       and encou
       offers monetary incentives to help boost Feedbacker engagement and transparency with your
       of f e r s moneta r y incenti v es to help boost  F eedbac k er engagement and t r anspa r ency with  y our
       company. .
            y
       compan
       Li v e  &  In t e r a c t i v e
       Live & Interactive
       Live Reaction connects you to real-time Feedback, allowing you to reshape your marketing
       Li v e  R eaction connects  y ou to  r eal-time  F eedbac k , all o wing  y ou to  r eshape  y our mar k eting
       strategy and achieve results.
       st r ate g y and achi ev e  r esults.
                                                Gain Valuable Insights
                                                G a i n   V a l uable  I ns i gh t s
                         e
                           v
                             di
                                      r
                                                       ghly
                                               r
                                                             r
                              e
                                                             ie
                                                              n
                        r
                              r
                                                                  n
                                                                   y
                          e
                                                                  i
                                                                ed
                           i
                            e
                                                               c
                                                                    o
                                       om
                                                       i
                                                 w
                         c
                                  si
                                    t
                                                           xp
                                          ee
                                             c
                                           dba
                                                  ho a
                                                          e
                                              k
                                                                     ur
                                                     e
                                   gh
                                                     r
                      ou

                                     s
                                                s
                                      f
                               c
                      Y You receive direct insights from Feedbackers who are highly experienced in your
                                                       h
                                 in
                                               e
                                t
                                         F
                                                            e
                               y
                               r
                             st
                        c
                         i
                         f
                      s specific industry. .
                      p
                       e
                         i
                           ndu
                           i
                          c
 U
 NTS IS TH
 Y
 , SO WH
 O
 '
 N
 O
 , THERE
 E
 T TODAY, THERE'S SO MUCH NOISE, SO WHAT REALLY COUNTS IS THE
 S
 E
 D
 I
 A
 A
 L
 U
 T
 A
 RE
 S SO M
 Y
 CH
 O
 C
 L
 C
 T
 A
 T
 I
 Y OF
 UNI
 OMM
 C
 QUALITY OF COMMUNICATION, AND IDEACOIL HELPS ME TO ACHIEVE

 T
 E
  H
 ELP
 S M
 O
 E
 V
 E
 I
 QUA
 A
 CH
 IL
 D
 I
 D
 N
 , A
 N
 C
 O
 O
 A
 LI
 E
                                               Reliable, Fast & Private
 THAT. THEY KNOW HOW TO ASK THE RIGHT QUESTIONS.
 TH A T .  TH E Y  KN O W H O W  T O  A S K  TH E   RI GHT Q UE S T I O N S .  R e l iab l e,   F a s t   &  P r i v a t e
                                                    e
                                                               t
                                                               r
                                                            e
                                                             r
                                                               u
                                                                    o
                                                                    ng
                                                                s
                                                                 t am
                                                       hel
                                                         p
                                                      t
                                                     o

                                                           s
                                                            t
                                                          f
                                                          o
                          o
                            c
                                e
                                         e
                           l
                              at
                                         ngaging d
                           i
                         c
                                                alogu
                       Ideacoil creates an upbeat, engaging dialogue to help foster trust among
                              e
                                s an upbeat,
                                                i
                             r
                       Idea
                                                             u
                                                              r
                                r
                                                            y
                                 s and
                               e
                              c
                               k
                                                             o
                         F
                          e
                                                                  ome
                                                                     s
                                                                     r
                         Feedbackers and your company. Through our system, your customers
                                                                us
                                                               c

                           e
                                                                 t
                           dba
                                                       y
                                      u
                                     o
                                                        stem,
                                        o
                                             . Th
                                                      s
                                        c
                                       r
                                         m
                                             y
                                           an
                                                ough our
                                          p
                                                r
                                     y
 OUTREACH MUSIC FESTIVAL & ACADEMY, SCHWAZ, AUSTRIA
 OUTR E A CH M U S I C FE S T I V A L  &  A C ADEM Y , SCH W AZ, AU S TR I A  p provide faster, higher quality reviews that only you have access to. .
                                                                cc
                                             y
                                                                  e

                                                 w
                                               v
                                                i
                                                e
                                                                     o
                                                                  s
                                              r
                                                  s that
                                              e
                                                                   s t
                                            t
                                    , higher qual
                                                          o
                                f
                                                             a
                                                         y
                                  t
                                   e
                                                           u h
                                   r
                                 as
                             v
                                                      o
                            o
                                            i
                            r
                                                       nly
                              de
                              i
                                                              e a
                                                              v]]></page><page Index="4"><![CDATA[Addressing The Elephants In The Room

       I FEEL FEEDBACK TO BUSINESSES IS WONDERFUL, ESPECIALLY AS A               Are you finding that generic su r vey s and  r e vi ew s a r e no longer adding any  r eal  v alue to  y our
                                                                                      Are you finding that generic surveys and reviews are no longer adding any real value to your
       LOCAL PERSON IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, BECAUSE IT KEEPS A GREAT                                       customer  f eedback p r ocess?
                                                                                                             customer feedback process?
        RELATIONSHIP WHEN PEOPLE ARE GOOD TO YOU. WHAT MORE CAN                   How important is actionable  f eedback that all o w s  y ou to  f ocus  y our mar k eting activity on
                                                                                       How important is actionable feedback that allows you to focus your marketing activity on
           HAPPEN, BUT BETTER BUSINESS AND CUSTOMER SERVICE?                                         key profit dri v e r s  f or  y our business?
                                                                                                          key profit drivers for your business?
                                                                                 Have you g r o wn ti r ed of  f eedback that is n ’t completely tailo r ed to  y our unique  r equi r ements
                                                                                      Have you grown tired of feedback that isn’t completely tailored to your unique requirements
                      CATHEDRAL WINE, NEW YORK, NY                                              and as a  r esult, brings no clarity to  y our business?
                                                                                                     and as a result, brings no clarity to your business?
    How                                                                           What type  o f an im p ac d  t   i w n  o y uld  r p e r al duc t e   o   f r  ee dba c e k f r f o e m p ote av ti e al  n  c u y sto r m e r si s   n w ess o  a r e  g e nu i n e l y
                                                                                       What type of an impact would real-time feedback from potential customers who are genuinely
                                                                                                          -
                                                                                                                                        h
                                                                                                          tim
                                                                                                                           n
                                                                                                e
                                                                                                     o
                                                                                                                 vic
                                                                                                                     of
                                                                                                                r

                                                                                                               se
                                                                                                                       ring h
                                                                                                                                o
                                                                                           interest
                                                                                                                                    bu
                                                                                                                                         ?
                                                                                                                                 u
                                                                                                     ur
                                                                                                interested in your product or service offering have on your business?
                                                                                                         o
                                                                                                                              o
    To                                                                          Ideacoil An       sw   e r s The Cal     l
                                                                                     Ideacoil Answers The Call
    Use                                                                         Ideacoil is a business pe r so n r ’ o s solution to all of these challenges and mo r e to c r e this b e y w
                                                                                                                                          eate n
                                                                                     Ideacoil is a business person’s solution to all of these challenges and more to create new
                                                                                                      wth. As a trusted authority in
                                                                                                                            eedbac
                                                                                     opportunities for business growth. As a trusted authority in feedback, we achieve this by:
                                                                                                                           f
                                                                                           or business g
                                                                                          f
                                                                                                                                        ev
                                                                                                                                                :
                                                                                                                                  , we achi
                                                                                opportunities
                                                                                                                                 k
    Ideacoil                                                                           Identifying  y our ta y r ou tho r oughly unde r r stand  y our ideal custome r .  y our bu y er
                                                                                                                           e insight into
                                                                                                                 o
                                                                                                    get audience and p
                                                                                            Identifying your target audience and providing extensive insight into your buyer
                                                                                                                           v
                                                                                                                      e
                                                                                                                       xtensi
                                                                                                                  viding
                                                                                       personas so that
                                                                                            personas so that you thoroughly understand your ideal customer.
                                                                                            Providing a unique tool and process to solicit customer feedback with incentives, and
                                                                                       Providing a unique tool and p r ocess to solicit customer  f eedback with incenti v es, and
                                                                                                                         v
                                                                                                               r
                                                                                                               vices, or li
                                                                                                                      v
                                                                                                                       e
                                                                                                                        e
                                                                                                                         ent spectacles.
                              Start Re-Imagine
                                                                                                   y
                                                                                                    our p
                                                                                            help you optimize your products, services, or live event spectacles.
                                                                                                        oducts, se
                                                                                       help you optimize
                                                                                                       r
                       1      Design your interactive feedback questionnaire. Offer a   Delivering  r eal-time actionable data that  y ou can consistently implement into  y our  r s.
                                                                                            Delivering real-time actionable data that you can consistently implement into your
                                                                                                                  ospects that
                                                                                                                           ou can con
                                                                                                                                   ert into custome
                                                                                            business to attract more high-quality prospects that you can convert into customers.
                                                                                                                          y
                                                                                                                                  v
                                                                                                 r
                                                                                                  act mo
                                                                                                      r
                                                                                       business to att
                                                                                                       e high-quality p
                                                                                                                 r
                              custom reward to the Feedbackers in exchange for their
                                                                                            Leveraging the full power of purposeful feedback to help you meet crucial short-term
                              insights.                                                Leveraging the full p o wer of purposeful  f eedback to help  y ou meet crucial short-term
                                                                                            goals and propel your business towards long-term sustainable success.
                                                                                       goals and p r opel  y our business t o w a r ds long-term sustainable success.
                              Invite The Crowd
                       2      Invite current customers and industry Feedbackers to   IDEAC IDEACOIL ALLOWS ME TO GAIN ACCESS TO CONSTRUCTIVE AND
                                                                                                                               O
                                                                                                                                 N
                                                                                                                              C
                                                                                                                                          I
                                                                                                                                        T

                                                                                                                                          VE AND
                                                                                                                                       C
                                                                                                                                   T
                                                                                                                                  S
                                                                                                                                      U
                                                                                                                                    R
                                                                                                                  A
                                                                                                  W
                                                                                                 O
                                                                                                                     CESS
                                                                                                                    C
                                                                                                           O
                                                                                                         T
                                                                                                             G
                                                                                                    S ME
                                                                                                              AIN
                                                                                                L
                                                                                         O
                                                                                          I
                                                                                                                           T
                                                                                              L
                                                                                                                            O
                                                                                           L A
                              participate in your online or in-person events.
                                                                                    PERSO  N A LI ZED  I NS I GHTS F R OM  O THE R  P R O F ESS I ONALS A N D
                                                                                         PERSONALIZED INSIGHTS FROM OTHER PROFESSIONALS AND
     3     Understand Your Customer And Ratings                                                            THIS  THIS IS BIG!
                                                                                                                         !
                                                                                                                 I
                                                                                                                  S BIG
           Manage feedback from your personal dashboard. Analyze the data to find patterns
           and quickly determine what work needs to be recalibrated.]]></page><page Index="5"><![CDATA[Addressing The Elephants In The Room

 I FEEL FEEDBACK TO BUSINESSES IS WONDERFUL, ESPECIALLY AS A   Are you finding that generic su r vey s and  r e vi ew s a r e no longer adding any  r eal  v alue to  y our
           Are you finding that generic surveys and reviews are no longer adding any real value to your
 LOCAL PERSON IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, BECAUSE IT KEEPS A GREAT   customer  f eedback p r ocess?
                                 customer feedback process?
 RELATIONSHIP WHEN PEOPLE ARE GOOD TO YOU. WHAT MORE CAN   How important is actionable  f eedback that all o w s  y ou to  f ocus  y our mar k eting activity on
            How important is actionable feedback that allows you to focus your marketing activity on
 HAPPEN, BUT BETTER BUSINESS AND CUSTOMER SERVICE?  key profit dri v e r s  f or  y our business?
                               key profit drivers for your business?
      Have you g r o wn ti r ed of  f eedback that is n ’t completely tailo r ed to  y our unique  r equi r ements
           Have you grown tired of feedback that isn’t completely tailored to your unique requirements
 CATHEDRAL WINE, NEW YORK, NY  and as a  r esult, brings no clarity to  y our business?
                          and as a result, brings no clarity to your business?
 How  What type  o f an im p ac d  t   i w n  o y uld  r p e r al duc t e   o   f r  ee dba c e k f r f o e m p ote av ti e al  n  c u y sto r m e r si s   n w ess o  a r e  g e nu i n e l y
           What type of an impact would real-time feedback from potential customers who are genuinely
                              -
                                                            h
                               tim
                                                n
                    e
                         o
                                     vic
                                         of
                                     r

                                   se
                                           ring h
                                                     o
               interest
                                                        bu
                                                              ?
                                                      u
                          ur
                    interested in your product or service offering have on your business?
                             o
                                                  o
 To  Ideacoil An       sw  e r s The Cal     l
          Ideacoil Answers The Call
 Use  Ideacoil is a business pe r so n r ’ o s solution to all of these challenges and mo r e to c r e this b e y w
                                                              eate n
          Ideacoil is a business person’s solution to all of these challenges and more to create new
                          wth. As a trusted authority in
                                                eedbac
          opportunities for business growth. As a trusted authority in feedback, we achieve this by:
                                                f
               or business g
               f
                                                            ev
                                                                    :
                                                      , we achi
     opportunities
                                                     k
 Ideacoil   Identifying  y our ta y r ou tho r oughly unde r r stand  y our ideal custome r .  y our bu y er
                                                e insight into
                                     o
                        get audience and p
                 Identifying your target audience and providing extensive insight into your buyer
                                               v
                                          e
                                           xtensi
                                      viding
            personas so that
                 personas so that you thoroughly understand your ideal customer.
                 Providing a unique tool and process to solicit customer feedback with incentives, and
            Providing a unique tool and p r ocess to solicit customer  f eedback with incenti v es, and
                                             v
                                   r
                                    vices, or li
                                          v
                                           e
                                            e
                                              ent spectacles.
 Start Re-Imagine
                        y
                        our p
                 help you optimize your products, services, or live event spectacles.
                            oducts, se
            help you optimize
                            r
 1  Design your interactive feedback questionnaire. Offer a   Delivering  r eal-time actionable data that  y ou can consistently implement into  y our  r s.
                 Delivering real-time actionable data that you can consistently implement into your
                                      ospects that
                                               ou can con
                                                       ert into custome
                 business to attract more high-quality prospects that you can convert into customers.
                                               y
                                                       v
                      r
                      act mo
                           r
            business to att
                           e high-quality p
                                     r
 custom reward to the Feedbackers in exchange for their
                 Leveraging the full power of purposeful feedback to help you meet crucial short-term
 insights.  Leveraging the full p o wer of purposeful  f eedback to help  y ou meet crucial short-term
                 goals and propel your business towards long-term sustainable success.
            goals and p r opel  y our business t o w a r ds long-term sustainable success.
 Invite The Crowd
 2  Invite current customers and industry Feedbackers to   IDEAC IDEACOIL ALLOWS ME TO GAIN ACCESS TO CONSTRUCTIVE AND
                                                    O
                                                     N
                                                  C
                                                              I
                                                             T

                                                               VE AND
                                                            C
                                                        T
                                                      S
                                                          U
                                                         R
                                       A
                      W
                     O
                                         CESS
                                        C
                               O
                              T
                                 G
                        S ME
                                  AIN
                    L
             O
               I
                                               T
                   L
                                                O
                L A
 participate in your online or in-person events.
        PERSO  N A LI ZED  I NS I GHTS F R OM  O THE R  P R O F ESS I ONALS A N D
              PERSONALIZED INSIGHTS FROM OTHER PROFESSIONALS AND
 3  Understand Your Customer And Ratings  THIS  THIS IS BIG!
                                             !
                                      I
                                       S BIG
 Manage feedback from your personal dashboard. Analyze the data to find patterns
 and quickly determine what work needs to be recalibrated.]]></page><page Index="6"><![CDATA[ideacoil
                   id     e   acoi           l ®    ®




                             s.
                                                    w
                                                          r
                                                        a
                                      e
                                               R
                                         al

                                                  e
                                   R
              nsight
      al
 R e  R e al  I nsight s.   R e al  R e w a r ds .
                                                                  .
                                                             ds
             I
 LEVE R A G E  THE  P O WER OF  F EED B A CK E R S ®   T O ENHANCE C U S T OMER
    LEVERAGE THE POWER OF FEEDBACKERS  TO ENHANCE CUSTOMER
                                              ®
                          N
                                                       T
                                                  R
                                          N
                                                     W
                   N
                            D DRIV
                                     B
          EXPE EXPERIENCES AND DRIVE BUSINESS GROWTH
                                            ESS G
                                                   O
                                   E
                                                        H
                    CES A
               RIE
                                       U
                                        SI
  Highly ta r ge t ed ma r k et i ng has n e v er been mo r e  c r itical t o  busin e ss succes s  than it is  t od a y .
      Highly targeted marketing has never been more critical to business success than it is today.
       Ideacoil will put at your finger tips information to help you reach your business objectives.
  Ideacoi l w i ll  p u t  at  y our finge r  tip s  in f o r mat i on  t o h e lp  y ou  r each  y o ur bu s ine s s objecti v es .

                                                t
                                                i
                                             e
                                              b
                                             w
                                          ou
                                       sit
                                     v
                                               s
                                      i
                                           r
                                    e
                        f
                       n
                        or

                          ma
                    r
               For mo For more information, please visit our website at:
                     e
                      i

                                p
                                  as
                                 e
                                 l
                                                   t
                                                 e a
                            tio
                              n,
                                                    :
                          www.id e ac o il . c o m
                               www.ideacoil.com
                                   di
                                  s
                                     ect
                                    r
                              a
                        or cont or contact us directly at:
                               t u
                               c
                                          a
                                        y
                                           :
                                          t
                                       l
                                           0
                       Phone Phone: +1-646-752-0430
                             : +1-646
                                        043
                                    -
                                    752
                                       -
                      Email: t e a m @ id e ac o il . c o m
                           Email: team@ideacoil.com
                              FE A TURE :
                         FE A   TURE      :
 © 2021 Ideacoil L L C.  P -1002-5
      © 2021 Ideacoil LLC. P-1002-5]]></page></pages></Search>